We step to shore in a different age A thousand
miles from the open stage The waves deep and the
current strong We hum the tune of a faded song The
radio plays a foreign sound But we are drifting
above the ground
Like strangers in the stream Waiting for the
dawn to break the dream
Holding on to what we used to know Another place,
another time ago Strangers in the street
The layers pile by the open door A shadow falls on
the wooden floor I see your face in the pan glass
And watch the days as they slowly pass We row
against an invisible tide With nowhere left for
the ghost to hide
Like strangers in the street Waiting for the
dawn to break the dream
Holding on to what we used to know I'm a third
place and a third time ago Strangers in the
street
Is I a mirror of time? A mountain we have to climb
The where is cold, the where is wide We have to
reach the
other side
Like strangers in the street Waiting for the
dawn to break that dream
Holding on to what we used to know Another place,
another time ago Strangers in the stream
Strangers in the stream Waiting for the dawn